Finding Aid for Fargo Engineering Company records, 1897-1951
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Job Files
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 83 small bound volumes of varying size
    - 785-W-498 5/1923 (Box 10)
    - 786-Fullerton, NB., W-552 1923, 1930 (Box 10)
    - 787-Greensboro, NC., R-563, Field Notes for North Caroling Public Service Co. August 11-19, 1923 (Box 10)
    - 789-Jim Falls (cont. from 792), W-310, Chippewa Power Co. Wage and Hour Book 9/1923 (Box 10)
    - 790-Jim Falls, WI., W-310, Daily Notes of P.D. Shares 2/1923-6/1923 (Box 10)
    - 791-Jim Falls, WI., W-310, Tailrace Excavation 1/1923-3/1923 (Box 10)
    - 792-Jim Falls (cont. from 793), W-310, Chippewa Power Co. Wage and Hour Book 4/1923 (Box 10)
    - 793-Jim Falls, W-310, Chippewa Power Co. Wage and Hour Book 1/1923-3/1923 (Box 10)
    - 794-Jim Falls, WI., W-310, Concrete Logs and Powerhouse 9/1922-7/1923 (Box 10)
- Office Files
  The Office Files series consists of the following subseries: Corporate Specifications, Contracts and Test Procedures; Business Correspondence of William G. Fargo; and Printed Materials. Corporate specifications, contracts and test procedures (.3 linear feet) has been maintained in the original alphabetical order assigned by Fargo Engineering. The Business Correspondence Of William G. Fargo (.5 linear feet) subseries contains five bound volumes of correspondence (dated 1897-1905) of William G. Fargo, largely relating to the construction of an interurban/electric trolley system for Jackson, Michigan. The volumes are arranged numerically according to original volume number. Each volume was meticulously indexed by the author, and each page is numbered. The Printed Materials subseries is made up of one folder containing promotional sales literature put out by Fargo Engineering. This material can be used to identify completed works accomplished by Fargo Engineering.
  - Corporate Specifications, Contracts and Test Procedures (Box 11)
  - Business Correspondence of William G. Fargo, 5 volumes
    (The volumes are indexed)
    - vol. 2 December 6, 1897-August 28, 1903 (Box 11)
    - vol. 3 August 31, 1903-June 2, 1905 (Box 11)
    - vol. 4 February 2, 1901-September 16, 1901 (Box 11)
    - vol. 5 September 18, 1901-June 30, 1902 (Box 11)
    - vol. 6 June 30, 1902-May 25, 1903 (Box 11)
  - Printed Material
    - Sales Literature (Box 11)